bytelove.com 2008-12-17

# Privacy Policy - Geek, Gamer and WoW T-shirts & Gear | bytelove.com

Privacy Policy

###   
What information does Bytelove AB collect?

Bytelove asks for billing and shipping address information at the time of checkout. Address information is not sold to third party companies; all information is kept private.   

Bytelove never sees your payment information.  Payment procedures are handled by our partners WorldPay and PayPal on their secure servers.

Upon checkout and to the right in our product catalog, the customer is asked if they would like to be included in our newsletter. This is not required and if the customer does not check this box, the denial is honored. If you choose not to be included, you will not receive newsletters or mass emails from us. If you do choose to receive our newsletter, either via ordering or the subscribe box in the sidebar, you can easily unsubscribe by following the instructions at the bottom of our newsletter.

### What are "cookies" and how does Bytelove use them?

Bytelove uses cookies to track your current shopping cart. Cookies are small bits of data that are sent to your browser and stored on your hard drive. We require that cookies be turned on (in your browser) in order to use this site.

We also collect IP addresses and browser information, through Google Analytics, in order to report on referrers, demographics and technology used by our visitors. 

### With whom do we share your information and for what purpose?

Bytelove does not sell, rent, or trade your personal information with others. Your browser and cookie data are shared with Google Analytics.

We only use the information to ship your order and to help make this site better.

### Your consent

By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by Bytelove AB as outlined in this Privacy Policy.
